packexpo.com 2008-05-12

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

BDMetrics, Inc. ("BDMetrics") is concerned about your privacy and the confidentiality of the information you share with us. The purpose of this privacy statement is to disclose the privacy practice of BDMetrics and this site (the "Site"). If you have any questions about this privacy statement, please contact us by email at ProfessionalServices@BDMetrics.com.

**What personally identifiable information is collected on the Site?**  
A User is a person who uses the site. In the course of its registration process, BDMetrics collects certain personally identifiable information. Personally identifiable information is information that can be traced back to a single User. A User who provides personally identifiable information in order to register for the site is a Registered User. A Registered Users may be a company or an individual, and may have access to all or portions of the site, including distinct and/or overlapping portions of the site depending on that Registered Users role. Names, physical addresses, and email addresses are examples of personally identifiable information that is collected during the registration process.

Certain additional information is also collected in an aggregate form and used solely in connection with improving the performance and responsiveness of our services and the Site. This information includes a User's originating domain, time of visit, connection speed, domain names, and internet service provider. This information is not personally identifiable information and there is no attempt to correlate such information to an individual User.

**How is the information collected and maintained?**  
Any personally identifiable information collected by BDMetrics is provided directly by Users in the course of the registration process or in connection with updating such information. BDMetrics does not use third parties to collect such information. Such information is password protected and Users alone control the content and accuracy of their personally identifiable information; however, BDMetrics may retain in backup or inactive files the uncorrected or outdated form of data that is corrected or updated. Such data may be retained for several reasons, including technical constraints, dispute resolution purposes, troubleshooting and enforcement of agreements. Users have access to their individual information at all times and may update or correct it at any time. If Users believe that there are errors in their information that they cannot correct by accessing the Site, they can contact ProfessionalServices@BDMetrics.com for assistance.

**Will BDMetrics use personally identifiable information to contact Users?**  
From time-to-time, BDMetrics will send Registered Users Site and service announcement updates by email. Active Users may not un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the Site and service. In addition, BDMetrics may request individual Users to complete surveys on a voluntary basis regarding their use of the Site in order to gather information to be used in improving the Site.

**Is the information shared and/or transferred?**  
Access to Registered Users' personally identifiable information is restricted to other Registered Users of the Site. Personally identifiable information will be not transferred or sold to third parties who are not Registered Users. Notwithstanding the foregoing, BDMetrics will divulge personally identifiable information to law enforcement agencies or other governmental agencies when required to do so or when BDMetrics in good faith believes it is necessary in order to comply with legal obligations. In addition, in the event that BDMetrics or substantially all of its assets are acquired or merged into another entity, personally identifiable information may be transferred to the successor in interest. 

The BDMetrics system is designed to optimize the User's experience by converting search results into an optimized recommendation list. Certain user selections such as book-marking or planned visits may result in recommendations of products, services, or companies. Such recommendations may include opportunities for the User to schedule meetings with companies. 

**Are "cookies" used by the Site?**  
Cookies are used by BDMetrics to verify an individual User's access to discrete areas of the Site. Such use of cookies is required for a User to access and use the Site. Upon a User's login, a cookie is written to a User's browser containing an encrypted version of the User's user identification including authorized role. This information is sent to our Site during the course of the User's navigation and use of the Site. Cookies or information contained in a cookie are not shared with any other website or third party.

**Does the Site use "log files"?**  
When Users visit the Site, they automatically disclose certain information to our server, such as Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user's movement through the Site, and to gather broad demographic information for use on an aggregate basis. IP addresses and other similar information collected through log files are not associated with individual Users.

**What type of security is employed by the Site?**  
BDMetrics Inc. knows data confidentiality and security are extremely important. We take many precautions to ensure your information is safe and secure. Use of the Site by Registered Users is password-protected. Only Registered Users and BDMetrics personnel (solely on a need to know basis) have access to such information. The BDMetrics.com web site uses Thawte (a subsidy of Verisign) Secure Socket Layer (SSL) Certificates, an industry-standard encryption technology which encrypts all organization and participant data transmitted over the web. This highly advanced technology prevents unauthorized people from reading the data that you send over the web. BDMetrics also encrypts passwords and credit card numbers in the BDMetrics password protected database. Credit card numbers are stored for the ease of use for returning licensees. All information collected from Registered Users by BDMetrics is stored on servers hosted in a physically secure environment. Questions about the security of the Site should be directed to ProfessionalServices@BDMetrics.com. Notwithstanding the foregoing, Users should keep in mind that this Site and the BDMetrics services are run on software, hardware and networks, any component of which may, from time to time, require maintenance or experience problems or breaches of security. 

**Is the Site connected to other websites by "links"?**  
BDMetrics may provide links to the websites of a limited number of third parties. BDMetrics is not responsible for the content, reliability, security, or privacy practices of these websites. This Privacy Policy applies solely to this Site.

**How are Users notified of changes in the Policy?**  
From time-to-time, BDMetrics may update this Privacy Policy by posting a revised Policy on this web page. We will also post a notice on the Site's homepage. Changes to the Policy will take effect upon posting, provided that the use of any information previously collected by BDMetrics will continue to be governed by the Policy in effect when the information was gathered.
